

Matteo Rizzi

matteo@rizzi.xyz







Bachelor in Computer Science, Junior Research Scientist

I am an Junior Research Scientist in the Security and Trust unit at FBK. I joined the S&T unit to explore and improve TLS analysis and delve into identity management. I am working concurrently between FBK and the Istituto Poligrafico e Zecca dello Stato.

Experiences

Fondazione Bruno Kessler (Trento, Italy)

Junior Research Scientist ● Feb, 2021 - Present

Security analysis of the TLS deployments of IPZS projects, TLS Analysis in Android Apps and TLS tool enhancement within the Security & Trust research unit.

Internship ● *Feb, 2020 - May, 2020*

Study and improvement of TLS analysis tools within the Security & Trust research unit.

Futuro & Conoscenza S.r.l. (Trento & Rome, Italy)

Junior Research Scientist • Jul, 2021 - Present

Collaboration between <u>Fondazione Bruno Kessler</u> and <u>IPZS</u> to promote the exchange of know-how and competences in the field of security technologies (material and digital) such as identification and anti-counterfeiting, as well as the creation of a center for the coordination and exploitation of research.

Projects

breaking-telegram

PoC script to break Telegram • 2021

Simple PoC script that allows you to exploit telegram's "send with timer" feature by saving any media received with this functionality, automatically.

TLSAssistant

Version 1.3 and 2.0 to 2.3 • 2020 - Present

Fully-featured tool that combines state-of-the-art TLS analyzers with a report system that suggests appropriate mitigations and shows the full set of viable attacks.

iHashDNA

Perceptual hashing library in python ● 2020 - Present

Python library to easily check if two images are similar without machine learning by using Perceptual Hashing (phash and whash combined), with ban and unban image system.

Minor Works

Mallodroid

Conversion in Python 3 and enhancements • 2020 - 2021

telegram-deep-fakes-bot

Easy implementation and use of the first order model ● 2020

Rappresentanti Bot

HelpDesk Telegram bot to support DISI Students in University of Trento ● 2019

Education

University of Trento (Trento, Italy)

Bachelor of Computer Science • Sept, 2017 - Mar, 2021

Thesis in TLS Analyzers for Android Apps - State-of-the-art Analysis and Integration in TLSAssistant

I.I.S. Primo Levi (Badia Polesine, Italy)

High School Diploma ● Sept, 2012 - Sept, 2017

Final elaborate in psychoanalysis of James Joyce and the artificial intelligences

Certifications

CyberWiser - CyberRange And Capacity Building in CyberSecurity

Module	Date	Certificate
P-01-M-01	May 19, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-01-M-02	May 20, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-02	May 20, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-03	May 20, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-04	May 25, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-05	June 4, 2021	<u>Download</u>
P-06	June 4, 2021	<u>Download</u>

First Certificate

Cambridge Assessment English - B2 ● Apr, 2017

ECDL Base

ECDL / ICDL Certification ● May, 2016

Soft Skills

University of Trento (Trento, Italy)

Student Representative for DISI • Nov, 2018 - Nov, 2022

Department Of Information Engineering And Computer Science



